meeting of the Miami Special Utility Authority for today's day. I am number two as
invocation by a pastor of a spot at a pustalic facility.
Sure, soon to be great, sir. Yes, I feel sorry. Thank you for being here, Phil.
Thank you. Would you bow your heads with me?
Father, we thank you tonight for just a community where we come and open up a leadership meeting
such as this, the City Council and we open up with prayer acknowledging your sovereignty,
acknowledge your presence and we ask God as you continue protect our community.
I'll be with these leaders tonight, give them wisdom and give them unity as they conduct
the business of our community. Continue to keep us God's safe with the help of those policemen,
keep them safe also in their service and the firemen and all those that serve those citizens
of this community. We ask this in Jesus name. Amen. Amen. Thank you. Thank you.
United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands. One nation under by the invisible
with liberty and justice for us. I did number four is public input and unscheduled personal
appearances. Anyone in the audience it wishes to address the special utility authority.
They're being none. I don't find as a consent agenda staff is recommending items six through eight
for the consent agenda. There's no discussion on those items. We'll entertain a motion.
We're on my commotion. We'll provide them six through eight in the consent agenda.
Okay, we have a second. Second. Roll call. Johnson.
Weston. I. Forester. Hi. Lewis. Hi. Show. Hi.
I am nine well state bank contract and resolution to process utility payments for the City of Miami,
Jill. Yes. We are beginning a remodel of the customer service at which time the drive
through will be closed. They're going to move over there on the 25th of May but the construction won't
start until the 6th. We want to give them a few days to make sure all the bugs are worked out before we
have to deal with construction. During the because we knew we were going to close on the drive through one of the
other things we thought about was seeing if there's some banks that might be able to take our utility
payments. So we spoke with all banks and one stood out in particular that actually fit exactly
what we needed the process that we needed to go through the timing that we needed and that was
well state bank. They have they're going to end up with two locations. They have one that's right by Walmart.
They also take other utility payments. I believe it's gas. The second one on Steve Owens, it's not quite
open yet. They're going to have a soft opening on May 23rd and then they're hoping to have the grand opening
the end of June, probably about the 27th he said. If you approve this agreement and then there's a
resolution attached to it also because they required us to have a resolution to say specifically.
who's going to be the ones to be able to conduct business on our account.
So if you approve all of this, we plan to have them in place and taking payments by the 30th.
Hopefully sooner, but no way to the 30th, which is Monday.
And the branch out by the turnpike you said will be open, the soft opening is on the 23rd,
so it will be open before the 30th.
Yes.
Okay.
And how do we plan on communicating this with the public?
Well, we've been passing out flyers right now.
I've got one ready in the queue to start passing out tomorrow and Facebook website.
We're talking about the remodel now with the flyer.
We've been doing that for two or three weeks, but then we'll have a revised one that will go out.
And is there going to go in the statements also?
Yes.
That was one of the things we wanted to do to also.
So the customer will still have the option to come inside and tell you that.
Yes.
They will actually be located just south of where they're at right now.
It's literally across from my office door.
It's kind of, we'll have signage, we'll have it all roped off and then signage to lead them
to the right spot.
Okay.
So in how long of a period do you anticipate the remodel attack?
No more than five weeks.
We're actually anticipating 14 days, but we want to give this a please time just in case something
happens.
Well, it's five weeks with the additional days, them just being over there without starting
construction.
So customer, Jay, need to come inside for any reason, just as in the past can continue to
come inside.
Those that have utilized the drive through or asking them to use Welch.
Yes.
That's the drive through.
We'll get in the drop-off.
We'll still stay there.
We actually have two drop-boxes.
We're debating whether to leave the one drive through the main drive through open because there's
a drop-box there also, but we'll check those more often during the day.
And they can also pay online, is that correct?
They can pay with the credit card.
There's also automatic draft through their bank account that we could set up for.
We're not currently taking advantage of that, but this would be a good time.
Yeah.
We think so too.
One thing that I think's important to point out too is we're going to evaluate this at the
end.
And there's a very real possibility we may ask you to make this permanent.
We have our staff.
It would free up a lot of our staff's time to be able to do some additional work.
We would be compensating by having two locations instead of one.
And if everything works out well with Welch State Bank, people still will always have to come
inside if they're setting up their services or have any issues with their bill.
We never do that at the drive through.
And we would still leave the drop-box open here as well.
So we just wanted to see how it would work.
And with this remodeling, this is a really good opportunity too.
That's a prize by the number of people that still drive through and pay the bill.
20.
That's about 2,300 a month.
1,300 a month.
Yeah.
We put a counter on just to say, I'm one of them.
I'm fine, I'm going to say that thing.
What are you saying is that?
It's frifting.
Okay.
Any other questions for Jill?
I don't know.
I haven't.
So right now this is a temporary process.
We're not approving eliminating the drive through.
Forever.
We're just approving the temporary process.
And this is only a premium temporary.
Okay.
And this is just for real estate bank to take our utility payments.
The resolution that they required from us.
Okay.
Any other questions?
David any concerns?
No, sir.
Thank you.
We have a motion.
I'll make a motion.
And a second.
I'll second it.
A roll call, please.
For aster?
I do.
You can take your younger generations.
You can take your parents.
You have to reflect on the contrary.
You have to look at the government again.
If they are having spayed new to clinics which benefit the community, would we be willing to do a utility waiver just during that time
when the animal shelters up and running everything will be transferred there.
I believe the average of bill comes to about $77 a month.
Okay.
Well, it's a valuable service that they provide to the community.
Any questions for Dean?
Mike emotion improvement.
I'll second down.
Roll properly.
Two.
I don't believe it.
Do you visit Dean and do you visit Dean and do you visit Dean?
Not on the CGMB.
You're on staff reports or in your packet in questions for staff on any items.
They're an ungrusted announcements.
And item 14 is a journey.
We have a motion to adjourn.
Motion.
And a second.
Second.
Roll ball.
Four.
Two.
All right.
Okay.
We're going to take this a brief break.
The staff is ready.
We'll move.